AYESHA NOOR, 2D Artist

 $Rawalpindi,\,46000,\,Pakistan,\,+923339116434,\,brunetteartsy\,@\,gmail.com$

LINKS	LinkedIn, Behance, Artstation, Instagram			
PROFILE	Greetings, I'm a 2D Artist passionate about creating beautiful and engaging art for games, animation, and books. I've been working in the game industry for over 4 years, and I've had the opportunity to work on various projects. I'm passionate about my work.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Jan 2021 — May 2024	2D Artist, Mobify		Islamabad	
	 As a 2D artist, my primary focus is on crafting captivating visuals and artwork that breathe life into the game's characters, environments, and user interface elements. I also worked closely with other artists, developers, game designers, and the marketing team. As a game artist, I'm constantly honing my skills and staying up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies in the industry. 			
Nov 2020 — Dec 2021	Publication Designer, Taleemabad			Islamabad
	 Managed content creation and publication process for children coloring books, ensuring timely and accurate delivery of illustrations. 			
Sep 2020 — Nov 2021	Graphic Designer, Women Technology House			Islamabad
	• Utilized a variety of software to create high-quality visuals, including Adobe Photoshop, and Illustrator			
Apr 2016 — Present	Freelancer, Self-Employed			Islamabad
	I've been working on different freelancing websites and worked on multiple projects.			
EDUCATION				
Feb 2017 — Feb 2021	BS Computer Science, NUM	ЛL		Islamabad
SKILLS	Adobe Photoshop	Expert	Adobe Illustrator	Expert
	Z Brush	Skillful	Adobe After Effects	Experienced